ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Buffalo Labor Programs: Women at Work -- DVD 6 of 6 (Box 28.6)
- One Strike and You're Out!, 1 (Box 29)
  V64
- Reaching the out of school student, 2 (Box 29)
  V69
- Owen Beiber, 3 (Box 29)
  V68
- RTC, January 1995, 4 (Box 29)
- Sights Sounds of ANERA, AMBFLO Promo, 5 (Box 29)
- RTC-004 - Providing Protected Horizontal Mobility in Minutes, 6 (Box 29)
  V194
- Organizing: Assessing Our Level of Support, 1996; 7 (Box 29)
- 4-Hour House, 8 (Box 29)
  V191
- Teamsters and our communities: hand in hand, 1996; 9 (Box 29)
- Talk back to the Union Busters, 1996; 10 (Box 29)
- Smart Strategies: New Ways to fight our future, 1996; 11 (Box 29)
- RTC-011 -- Static Snaphook Roll-Out, 12 (Box 29)
- Two Nations -- One Union, 1996; 13 (Box 29)
  V188
- RTC-002 -- Guidelines for Development of an Effective Fall Protection Program, 14 (Box 29)
- Common Sense Economics: Module #1 - The Economy is not like the Weather, 15 (Box 29)
- Teamsters: Stronger than Ever, 1996; 16 (Box 29)
- Jeanne Rudski, 17 (Box 29)
- Deregulation in California - news Hour - Jim Lehrer, 18 (Box 29)
  V200
- Economics Education - Module #2 - Four Role Plays, 19 (Box 29)
  V197
- Actions Speak Louder than Words, 20 (Box 29)
  V176
- Ford-UAW -- AIS - Day 2, Tape #3 Day 3, Tape #1, 21 (Box 29)
- What You Say Matters, 1996; 22 (Box 29)
  V189
- VDTs in the workplace -- part 1-Health concerns; part 2-Strategies, 1 (Box 30)
- VDTs in the workplace -- part 1-Health concerns; part 2-Strategies, 2 (Box 30)
- VDTs in the workplace -- part 1-Health concerns; part 2-Strategies, 3 (Box 30)
- Tale of two plants, 4 (Box 30)
- You and your rights on the job / produced for the Labor Education Center, Southeastern Massachusetts University, 1988; 5 (Box 30)
- VDTs in the workplace -- part 1-Health concerns; part 2-Strategies, 7 (Box 30)
- Leadership without easy answers, 8 (Box 30)
  V206
- Studebaker, 9 (Box 30)
- Studebaker; Lou Holtz, 10 (Box 30)
- Outokumpu American Brass: Training TogetherOur Competitive Edge, 1995; 11 (Box 30)
  September 1995
- The Power of Vision: discovering the future series / Joel Arthur Barker, 12 (Box 30)
- Who's counting? /Marilyn Waring on Sex, Lies Global Economics, 1 (Box 31)
  V222
- Generation, 2 (Box 31)
  V232
- The Corporation: a film by Mark Achbar, Jennifer Abbott Joel Bakan, 3 (Box 31)
- Booted Out!, 4 (Box 31)
- The Great Depression, 5 (Box 31)
- The Great Depression, 6 (Box 31)
- An Introduction to Ford 2000, 7 (Box 31)
  V49
- Cornell Industry Education Program: The History of Outokumpu American Brass, 8 (Box 31)
  V47
- Cornell Industry Education Program: The History of U.S.W.A., 9 (Box 31)
  V48
- Health Care Cost Containment, 10 (Box 31)
  V44
- Mock Arbitration, 11 (Box 31)
  V59
- Contract Admin. Mock Arbitration, 12 (Box 31)
  V58
- Labor Unions - 4/2/1987, 13 (Box 31)
  Nightline with Ted Koppel - Mind over myth -- 7/4/1987 ---- V52
- Changing attitudes: Union members talk about AIDS, 14 (Box 31)
  V22
- Ball State University, 15 (Box 31)
  V5
- the market of choice / Outokumpu Company, 16 (Box 31)
  V28
- Molly Dodd / Children at work -- 3/2/1991 // Danger at work-American undercover HBO -- 11/7/1991, 17 (Box 31)
- Changing Attitudes: Union Members talk about AIDS, 18 (Box 31)
  V23
- NYS AFL-CIO NYCOM present: The Case of the Safety and Health Hazards / narrated by Raymond Burr, 19 (Box 31)
  V19
- NYS AFL-CIO NYCOM present: The Case of the Safety and Health Hazards / narrated by Raymond Burr, 20 (Box 31)
- Between the netting, 21 (Box 31)
- Can't happen to me, 1 (Box 32)
  V124
- Chemical safety for laboratory workers, 2 (Box 32)
  V133
- American BrassAmerican Spotlight presents CSTV, 3 (Box 32)
  V132
- Dancing with the bogeyman, Dr. Morris Massey 1991, 4 (Box 32)
- Never surrender, HERE #26, 5 (Box 32)
  V139
- Ford/UAW leadership "Many faces", 6 (Box 32)
- Ford/UAW leadership "Many faces", 7 (Box 32)
- First on the scene, 8 (Box 32)
- Collective Bargaining Session II, 11/4/1986, 9 (Box 32)
  V127
- Collective Bargaining Session 12, 11/15/1986, 10 (Box 32)
- Frontline: the Heartbeat of America, 11 (Box 32)
  V138
- As it should be done, 12 (Box 32)
- The Entrepreneurs: an American Adventure, 13 (Box 32)
  V129
- VDTs in the work environment -- Issues for union leaders, 14 (Box 32)
- Barry Bluestone - Economics I, 15 (Box 32)
  V116
- Cornell Industry Education Program: The World Economy, 16 (Box 32)
  V112
- Automotive Industry Studies (AIS) - Program Meeting Notification -- 4/8/1992, 17 (Box 32)
- Burn Hazards in Aluminum Reduction and Fabricating Facilities, 18 (Box 32)
  V118
- Pre-Retirement Planning -- 10/6/1978, 19 (Box 32)
- A New Voice for American Workers -- September 1995, 1 (Box 33)
- Labor Unions Railroads: then now, 1999; 2 (Box 33)
- Ford Communications Network: UAW Panel Discussion - Part 2, 2000; 3 (Box 33)
  Reel #2 -- 4/28/2000
- Changing the Future with the Blueprint for the 1990's, 4 (Box 33)
- Right the First Time, 5 (Box 33)
- Meeting Robbers, 6 (Box 33)
- Right the first time, 7 (Box 33)
- Unmarked, 8 (Box 33)
- The Employer's Perspective, 9 (Box 33)
- Modifying and Customizing Reports, 10 (Box 33)
  tape six
- Mediation -- An alternative to court (w/0 closed captions); CADR/the Judiciary/State of Hawaii -- May 2000, 18 (Box 33)
- Tops Leadership Training - Entire Course (Box 34)
  - Tops Leadership Training - Entire Course, 1 (Box 34)
    pulled from box 30, ff 22, of /4283
- AIS Tour CD-ROM "Label" (Box 35)
  - AIS Tour CD-ROM "Label", 1 (Box 35)
    pulled from box 22, ff 55 or /4283
- AIS Tour: an electronic exploration for UAW, Ford, and Visteon employees and their families (Box 36)
  - AIS Tour: an electronic exploration for UAW, Ford, and Visteon employees and their families, 1 (Box 36)
    pulled from box 22, ff 55 of /4283
- Cornell - AIS Tour (Box 37)
  - Cornell - AIS Tour, 1 (Box 37)
- Champions -- 7/2/2003 (Box 38)
  - Champions -- 7/2/2003, 1 (Box 38)
    pulled from box 33, ff 38 of /4283
- Cornell O.C. 2/21/2000 (Box 39)
- 01066.dbt; 01066.doc (Box 40)
  - 01066.dbt; 01066.doc, 1 (Box 40)
    pulled from /4283 b92/ff6
- State Budget Crisis: Dean Lipsky's Message - 11/20/1990 (Box 41)
  - State Budget Crisis: Dean Lipsky's Message 11/20/1990, 1 (Box 41)
    pulled from /4283, box 132, ff 60
- Prospering in America / Congressman Jack Quinn -- 7/4/1993, 1 (Box 42)
  pulled from box 30, ff 13
- Prospering in America: Job Security -- 5/30/1993, 1 (Box 43)
  pulled from box 30, ff 14
- Prospering in America: Sexual Harassment -- 6/28/1993, 1 (Box 44)
  pulled from box 30, ff 15
- Prospering in America: NAFTA -- 6/6/1993, 1 (Box 45)
  pulled from box 30, ff 16
- Prospering in America: Healthcare -- 5/23/1993, 1 (Box 46)
  pulled from box 30, ff 17
- Prospering in America: International Unions -- 7/11/1993, 1 (Box 47)
  pulled from box 30, ff 18
- Prospering in America: labor Law Enforcement -- 6/13/1993, 1 (Box 48)
  pulled from box 30, ff 19
- National Public Radio, 1998; 1 (Box 49)
  pulled from box 30, ff 20
- Germany: 4/27/1992, 1 (Box 50)
  pulled from box 30, ff 21
- End 4/19/1989, 1 (Box 51)
  pulled from box 30, ff 22
- Germany cont. / Hans-Jrgen - 4/27/1992 --- United Kingdom / Tod Sullivan, 1 (Box 52)
  pulled from box 30, ff 23
- How to handle sexual harassment complaints, 1 (Box 53)
  pulled from box 30, ff 24
- 25 things to do if sexual harassment happens to you, 1 (Box 54)
  pulled from box 30, ff 25
- Six simple steps to stop sexual harassment, 1 (Box 55)
  pulled from box 30, ff 26
- United Kingdom cont. - 4/27/1992 / Tod Sullivan --- Tues 4/28/1992 - Sweden / John Fernandes, 1 (Box 56)
  pulled from box 30, ff 27
- Poland - Tues 4/28/1992 / Richard Kusziejko, Stanusaw Rudolf, 1 (Box 57)
  pulled from box 30, ff 28
- Tues 4/28/1992 -- North American Free / Beckman, Lee Smith, Harry katz, 1 (Box 58)
  pulled from box 30, ff 29
- Monday 4/27/1992 -- Unions and workers in the International Economy: Overview of Unions / Alex Blair, 1 (Box 59)
  pulled from box 30, ff 30
- Unions and Workers in the International Economy -- 4/12/1992 / Irving Bluestone, 1 (Box 60)
  pulled from box 30, ff 31
- unmarked, 1 (Box 61)
  pulled from box 30, ff 32
- Business in the schools, 1 (Box 62)
  pulled from box 30, ff 6 (1 of 2)
- Business in the Schools, 1 (Box 63)
  pulled from box 30, ff 6 (2 of 2)
- Ladders, 1 (Box 64)
  audio cassette
- Ladders, 1 (Box 65)
- Garden of ecstasy / Kay Gardner Sunwomyn Ensemble, 1 (Box 66)
- Avalon / Kay Gardner, 1 (Box 67)
  Solo flute meditations
- Mooncircles / Kay Gardner, 1 (Box 68)
- Emerging / Kay Gardner, 1 (Box 69)
- Future of heavy industry, 1 (Box 70)
- Managers and workers as partners, 1 (Box 71)
- Listening - final class, 1 (Box 72)
- Bernice Sandler: Women at Work: The Law is on Our Side -- 4/8/1991, 1 (Box 73)
- Labor History Minute #1, 1 (Box 74)
- Chemical Safety for Lab Workers, 1 (Box 75)
- Recognizing and Identifying Hazardous Materials - Unit II, 1 (Box 76)
- Recognizing and Identifying Hazardous Materials - Unit I, 1 (Box 77)
- Recognizing and Identifying Hazardous Materials - Unit III, 1 (Box 78)
- Recognizing and Identifying hazardous Materials - Unit IV, 1 (Box 79)
- Creating the Future of Continuing Education - 4/17/1988, 1 (Box 80)
- Morning Edition -- 1/7/1998 / National Public Radio, 1 (Box 81)
- Off Center / George Meany Center's Audio Magazine: v.1 (1990), 1 (Box 82)
- Off Center / George Meany Center's Audio Magazine: v.1 (1991), 1 (Box 83)
- Ben Bidwell / Chrysler Corporation, 1 (Box 84)
- Roy Roberts / Navistar International, 1 (Box 85)
- Hazardous Decomposition Synthetic Products in Firefighters -- 11/7/1990, 1 (Box 86)
- Prospering in America -- 8/15/1993 / DOL-Commissioner John Hudacs wk 13, 1 (Box 87)
- Prospering in America wk 12, 8/8/1993 / Horizons Waterfront Commission, Inc., 1 (Box 88)
- Prospering in America, 7/25/1993 / Executive Compensation Wk 10, 1 (Box 89)
- Prospering in America - 7/18/1993 / Indust'l. Dev. Agencies -- week 9, 1 (Box 90)
- International Labor Organizations the International Economy / Peter Coldrick, John Christensen, 1 (Box 91)
- Gil Scott-Heron, 1 (Box 92)
- Norm Chomsky World Bank IMF Gatt, 1 (Box 93)
- Industrial Relations Cassette-of-the-month / vol. 1, no. 7, 1 (Box 94)
- Nellie J. Brown - Operating Eng. -- Basic Toxicology -- 4/4/1989, 1 (Box 95)